[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Can I dare to dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "You can dare to dream all you want, but I don't want you to have those hopes crushed as soon as you get them up, Piers, because we've all seen movies like this before in Washington.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "CD", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Does the government reopen pending those deliberations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "You know, because they're not speaking to one another, it's a very hard question to answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What is the matter with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, there's absolutely nothing the matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "They are lying items in a budget and if you are going to look at a budget, at appropriations, at a funding mechanism you have to say, \"Where are we spending this money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "``", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "ORGAN: OK, we'll do a deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Where is the point where you think this could be honorably settled?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "I'll throw it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "... where can we get these reductions?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I'm calling an end to this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Now, Cathy I know that you're speaking from your hospital bed, how are you physically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I'm a lot better than I was, I'll tell you that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cathy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "How do you feel about the Washington politicians which are causing all this disruption all over your country leading in your case to a potentially very serious situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Well, I think that what really, really got to me and, you know, first we see people every year, the same people every year who were having the shutdown very reluctantly of something that they truly believe in.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "But is it -- but it's the calm before the storm, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Or it's the calm that comes from believing that there is no storm coming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 290, "question": "And Kelly on a certain sympathy when I heard President Obama said today, you know, it's like somebody fire bombing your house, stealing all your possessions, taking your car, and they're saying let's negotiate, what's the matter with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "That's a ridiculous analogy, but I was very glad that ...", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Kelly", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Is this part of a secret plan to run for the White House?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I'm speaking to a couple of groups in our senate right meeting in Iowa's is tomorrow morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "So, look, I'm up for a short-term debt deal, what is that deal likely to be, likely to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Yeah, look we take a deep breath, every president has negotiated on debt ceilings.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1979"]}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "EX", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "He's been having treatment for cancer and no cartilage left in his knees, what do you make of this Joyce?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Well, number one, we've had the house since 1979 but we never ever stayed down there except maybe 26 days out of the first 13 years because we had a ranch and we were busy and we didn't really get to go down there that much.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joyce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What do you feel about what's happened to your parents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I'm very frustrated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "He's lost his trust in everything at this point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "And where are they living in the moment, your parents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "My parents are relocated into town.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Marc Lamont Hill, what are worst things about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "It's not even work.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marc Lamont Hill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Oh, so you're doing it because you haven't been able to get the subsidies ready for the businesses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Well, then if businesses don't get subsidies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "They came out today and said, \"Wow, this is really worrying, America may not pay as back the money,\" (inaudible) right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "''", ":", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "They always get paid.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131008pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "So last people who get paid will be the Americans on Social Security, I mean this is a fuzz, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Oh yeah, and it's embarrassing, but I think we're not at a point yet where it's really impacting the willingness of people to buy our bonds, I think we've been able to explain to the Chinese and the Japanese that they will get paid in a way that has them laughing at us a little bit, but it doesn't have them panicking yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]